Everyone saw the market today — but
this is the part they missed.
The Nifty IT index sank about 2.7%
on June 30, sharply underperforming
the Nifty 50 (-0.34%) and extending
its losing streak to a third straight
session (down roughly
IT is among the most heavily weighted
sectors in Indian benchmarks and is
highly export-/US-demand-sensitive.
A move to a three-year low with multiple
52-week lows signals deepening pessimism
on US
For educational context only: the
IT drawdown is tied to macro (US rate
outlook) and structural (AI-disruption)
concerns rather than a single company
event - a
Understand the Indian market better
with Maven. trymaven.in.